// Questions - Midnights

export const midnightsQuestions = [
      {
    "question": "I'm damned if I do give a damn what people say ",
    "answers": ["Anti-Hero", "Lavender Haze", "Bejewelled", "Karma"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "You were standin' hollow-eyed in the hallway ",
    "answers": ["Snow on the Beach", "Labyrinth", "Question...?", "Maroon"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "It's me, hi, I'm the problem, it's me",
    "answers": ["Anti-Hero", "Midnight Rain", "Sweet Nothing", "Mastermind"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "This scene feels like what I once saw on a screen",
    "answers": ["You're On Your Own Kid", "The Great War", "Snow on the Beach", "Paris"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "I search the party of better bodies Just to learn that my dreams aren't rare",
    "answers": ["High Infidelity", "You're On Your Own Kid", "Glitch", "Could've, Would've, Should've"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "And he never thinks of me except for when I'm on TV",
    "answers": ["Anti-Hero", "Kama", "Bejewelled", "Midnight Rain"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Did you wish you'd put up more of a fight",
    "answers": ["Question...?", "Lavender Haze", "Paris", "The Great War"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Did all the extra credit, then got graded on a curve",
    "answers": ["Mastermind", "High Infidelity", "Bejewelled", "Dear Reader"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "You know how scared I am of elevators",
    "answers": ["Karma", "Labyrinth", "Midnight Rain", "Glitch"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Aren't you envious that for you it's not?",
    "answers": ["The Great War", "Could've, Would've, Should've", "Dear Reader", "Karma"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "Industry disruptors and soul deconstructors",
    "answers": ["Sweet Nothing", "Hits Different", "Paris", "Anti-Hero"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I'm the wind in our free-flowing sails",
    "answers": ["Bejewelled", "Question...?", "Mastermind", "Snow on the Beach"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "Argumentative, antithetical dream girl ",
    "answers": ["Labyrinth", "Hits Different", "Dear Reader", "Anti-Hero"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "I drew curtains closed, drank my poison all alone",
    "answers": ["The Great War", "Maroon", "Snow on the Beach", "Karma"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "Every single thing to come has turned into ashes",
    "answers": ["Sweet Nothing", "Could've, Would've, Should've", "Mastermind", "Bigger than the Whole Sky"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "I'm so in love that I might stop breathing",
    "answers": ["The Great War", "Paris", "Labyrinth", "Glitch"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Your picket fence is sharp as knives",
    "answers": ["Dear Reader", "Maroon", "High Infidelity", "Question...?"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "A brief interruption, a slight malfunction",
    "answers": ["Glitch", "Karma", "Midnight Rain", "Anti-Hero"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "The tomb won't close, stained glass windows in my mind",
    "answers": ["High Infidelity", "Sweet Nothing", "Bejewelled", "Could've, Would've, Should've"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "No one sees when you lose when you're playing solitaire",
    "answers": ["Anti-Hero", "Dear Reader", "Maroon", "Snow on the Beach"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "Get it off your chest, get it off my desk ",
    "answers": ["Karma", "The Great War", "Lavender Haze", "Bigger than the Whole Sky"],
    "correct": 2
    },

    {
    "question": "The burgundy on my T-shirt when you splashed your wine into me",
    "answers": ["Maroon", "Mastermind", "Hits Different", "Question...?"],
    "correct": 0
    },

    {
    "question": "I have this thing where I get older but just never wiser ",
    "answers": ["Labyrinth", "Midnight Rain", "Lavender Haze", "Anti-Hero"],
    "correct": 3
    },

    {
    "question": "And time can't stop me quite like you did",
    "answers": ["The Great War", "Snow on the Beach", "Paris", "Dear Reader"],
    "correct": 1
    },

    {
    "question": "He wanted it comfortable, I wanted that pain ",
    "answers": ["Karma", "High Infidelity", "Midnight Rain", "Could've, Would've, Should've"],
    "correct": 2
    },
];